╔══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════╗
║    ██████╗░░█████╗░██████╗░██╗██╗░░██╗██╗░░██╗░░███╗░░░░███╗░░  ██████╗░░█████╗░███████╗         ║
║    ██╔══██╗██╔══██╗██╔══██╗██║╚██╗██╔╝╚██╗██╔╝░████║░░░████║░░  ██╔══██╗██╔══██╗██╔════╝         ║
║    ██████╔╝███████║██║░░██║██║░╚███╔╝░░╚███╔╝░██╔██║░░██╔██║░░  ██████╔╝██║░░╚═╝█████╗░░         ║
║    ██╔══██╗██╔══██║██║░░██║██║░██╔██╗░░██╔██╗░╚═╝██║░░╚═╝██║░░  ██╔══██╗██║░░██╗██╔══╝░░         ║
║    ██║░░██║██║░░██║██████╔╝██║██╔╝╚██╗██╔╝╚██╗███████╗███████╗  ██║░░██║╚█████╔╝███████╗         ║
║    ╚═╝░░╚═╝╚═╝░░╚═╝╚═════╝░╚═╝╚═╝░░╚═╝╚═╝░░╚═╝╚══════╝╚══════╝  ╚═╝░░╚═╝░╚════╝░╚══════╝ 2023    ║
╚═════════════════════════════╣ https://radixx11rce3.blogspot.com ╠════════════════════════════════╝

═══════════════════════════════════════════
█▀█ █▀▀ █░░ █▀▀ ▄▀█ █▀ █▀▀   █ █▄░█ █▀▀ █▀█
█▀▄ ██▄ █▄▄ ██▄ █▀█ ▄█ ██▄   █ █░▀█ █▀░ █▄█
═══════════════════════════════════════════

⦁ Date:       2023-11-08
⦁ Name:       Icecream Apps Patch
⦁ Version:    2.4
⦁ Type:       Patch
⦁ File:       Patch.exe
⦁ SHA256:     05732B23340450E6E58FFE3964B0C7581987B8FBE69999E2E772918BABAB38F6

════════════════════════════════════════
▀█▀ ▄▀█ █▀█ █▀▀ █▀▀ ▀█▀   █ █▄░█ █▀▀ █▀█
░█░ █▀█ █▀▄ █▄█ ██▄ ░█░   █ █░▀█ █▀░ █▄█
════════════════════════════════════════

⦁ Category:   Image Processing/PDF Utilities/Screen Capture/Screen Recording
⦁ Protection: License File/Custom
⦁ OS:         WinALL
⦁ Homepage:   https://icecreamapps.com

═════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
▀█▀ ▄▀█ █▀█ █▀▀ █▀▀ ▀█▀   █▀▄ █▀▀ █▀ █▀▀ █▀█ █ █▀█ ▀█▀ █ █▀█ █▄░█
░█░ █▀█ █▀▄ █▄█ ██▄ ░█░   █▄▀ ██▄ ▄█ █▄▄ █▀▄ █ █▀▀ ░█░ █ █▄█ █░▀█
═════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════

. Icecream Ebook Reader: One of the best EPUB readers that transforms your computer screen into a 
convenient top-notch ebook reader. The tool enables you to read ebooks in EPUB, MOBI, FB2, PDF and 
other popular formats. Manage your digital library on your PC, Windows-based laptop or PC tablet. 
This program also features the ability to turn pages, use bookmarks, add notes, translate text, 
search your library, track reading progress and much more.

. Icecream Image Resizer: Meet Icecream Image Resizer, an application designed to help you resize 
your images quickly and conveniently. Add multiple files and even whole folders with photos and 
resize them in seconds. Just select the destination folder and simply click the "Resize" button! 
The tool supports all major graphic formats such as JPEG, JPG, PNG, BMP and TIFF. You can also set 
the desired width and height values either manually or using presets while retaining the original 
aspect ratio if desired.

. Icecream PDF Converter: Software that lets you convert to and from PDF format. While converting 
DOC to PDF, EPUB to PDF, JPG to PDF and more, you can merge all files in one PDF document, as well 
as use various output file settings. You can convert PDF to JPG, BMP, EPS and other formats without 
any limits to pages or number of files. PDF Converter has a built-in PDF reader and supports 
password-protected files.

. Icecream PDF Editor: Software that enables you to edit PDF files easier than ever before. Get 
access to all the tools and PDF editing modes you need with the help of smart tools panel. You can 
edit text, add notes, redact, protect files, manage pages and much more with the PDF editor. Learn 
how to edit a PDF document in a hassle-free way!

. Icecream PDF Split & Merge: An application that does exactly what it says; split and merge PDF 
files quickly and easily. You can split documents into single page files, get rid of specific 
pages, and more using the various splitting modes that the tool offers. Merge or split any PDF file 
without page quantity limitations and even work with password-protected files. The software also 
comes with a built-in PDF reader for more convenience. Combine PDF files in a hassle-free way.

. Icecream Photo Editor: The best photo editor and photo manager for Windows. Edit your pictures 
like a pro: add text and images, crop and resize, add filters, create collages and more with ease.

. Icecream Screen Recorder: A tool that enables you to capture any area of your screen either as a 
screenshot or a video file. The intuitive and easy-to-use software offers a complete suite of tools 
and options for professional screen capture with audio. With our screen recording software you can 
record webinars, games and Skype videos in HD, and much more in a quick and hassle-free way.

. Icecream Slideshow Maker: A software that you can use to create beautiful slideshows from your 
favorite photos. Breathe life into them by adding fancy transition effects and background audio. 
You don’t need to be tech savvy to create a multimedia slideshow with music in a few minutes; just 
add photos, configure slides transitions and durations, add a suitable music file, preview the 
project and simply press the "Create" button to enjoy the end result!

. Icecream Video Converter: Brand new video converter for Windows. Convert any of your videos via 
user-friendly GUI on a daily basis.

. Icecream Video Editor: Icecream Video Editor is an easy-to-use free video editing software for 
Windows that enables you to edit videos and create new ones from both videos and photos in a few 
minutes. Combine videos and photos, add transitions, trim videos, add titles and background audio, 
apply visual effects. You can also rotate, speed up, blur videos and much more.

. PDF Candy Desktop: PDF Candy Desktop is a versatile tool that enables you to convert files from 
PDF to various supported formats (PDF to DOC, PDF to JPG, etc), convert documents, ebooks and 
images to PDF, merge PDF, split PDF, extract images and text from PDF, edit PDF metadata, protect 
PDF and unlock password-protected PDF files. Most modes support processing files in a bulk. All 
these features are available through modern and user-friendly interface.

════════════════════════════════════
█░█ █▀█ █░█░█   ▀█▀ █▀█   █░█ █▀ █▀▀
█▀█ █▄█ ▀▄▀▄▀   ░█░ █▄█   █▄█ ▄█ ██▄
════════════════════════════════════

- Run the patch from any location you want or from the install location (optional).
- If the "Detect Install" option is ENABLED (by default), the patcher will try to detect the 
install location of the target products and patch all the files, without you having to specify a 
location.
- If the detection fails or the option is DISABLED, the patcher will try to use the current 
directory if its valid. Otherwise, it will ask you to select the correct folder.

TIP: The "Detect Install" option is also useful when you have multiple installs of the target 
products (editions/platforms) and you want to patch them all in one shot.

═════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
█▄░█ █▀▀ █░█░█ █▀   ▄▀█ █▄░█ █▀▄   █░█ █▀█ █▀▄ ▄▀█ ▀█▀ █▀▀ █▀
█░▀█ ██▄ ▀▄▀▄▀ ▄█   █▀█ █░▀█ █▄▀   █▄█ █▀▀ █▄▀ █▀█ ░█░ ██▄ ▄█
═════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════

In almost all my releases you will find a main menu. This menu can be opened by cliking the little
button with three lines (at top-left corner of the window). Among the options shown here, the two
most important are:

⦁ News & Announcements: This option will check if there is any important announcement that I want to
  share with the community. Generally, these announcements are also posted on the website.

⦁ Check for Updates: This option will check if an update of this release is available. If there is
  one, it will show information about the release and will give you the chance to download it
  directly. Normally any new version of this release will be posted on the website, with the
  exception of some cases in which I cannot publicly post such releases for "legal" reasons. In
  those cases, using this option is the only way to get a new version.

NOTE: These options require Internet access and will only connect to the net when selected. In case
      you have a firewall, probably you will need to make an exception.               

═══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
▄▀█ █▄░█ ▀█▀ █ █░█ █ █▀█ █░█ █▀   ▄▀█ █▄░█ █▀▄   █▀▀ ▄▀█ █░░ █▀ █▀▀   █▀█ █▀█ █▀ █ ▀█▀ █ █░█ █▀▀ █▀
█▀█ █░▀█ ░█░ █ ▀▄▀ █ █▀▄ █▄█ ▄█   █▀█ █░▀█ █▄▀   █▀░ █▀█ █▄▄ ▄█ ██▄   █▀▀ █▄█ ▄█ █ ░█░ █ ▀▄▀ ██▄ ▄█
═══════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════

Some antivirus can detect this release as a threat and try to remove it. The reason for this is
because my releases are packed/protected in order to reduce its size and avoid alterations to the
code. This protection can be erroneously identified as a threat, it is what is commonly known as a
FALSE POSITIVE. Just ignore it, it is safe to use.

IMPORTANT: there will be no risk when using my releases as long as you have downloaded it from the
links posted on my site or from the "Check for Updates" option. If you have downloaded this release
from another site, I CANNOT GUARANTEE ITS INTEGRITY. In such case, I will not take responsability
for eventual problems that arise when using it. Be careful!

As a precaution, always check the release hash.                               

════════════════════════════════════
█▀▄ █ █▀ █▀▀ █░░ ▄▀█ █ █▀▄▀█ █▀▀ █▀█
█▄▀ █ ▄█ █▄▄ █▄▄ █▀█ █ █░▀░█ ██▄ █▀▄
════════════════════════════════════

This release is provided AS IS for FOR EVALUATION PURPOSES ONLY!
If you can afford the software, please BUY IT. Support the developer to make a better product.